https://www.imageproductsca.com/privacy-statement/

HomePrivacy StatementPrivacy Statement
Privacy StatementIPCadminWP2018-05-24T19:50:36-04:00Updated: May 1, 2018We have updated our Privacy Policy to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that goes into effect on May 25, 2018. The GDPR is a privacy protection law enacted by the European Union (EU) impacting how companies collect and handle personal data of EU customer’s only.Even though Image Products of California has always operated within the USA, without any international offices, we still offer shipping to the EU. This puts us within the scope of complying with the GDPR, which requires us to update our privacy policy. The updated privacy policy is much more comprehensive and explicit, including specific sections regarding EU customer data.We respect your privacy, regardless if you are in the USA, EU, or anywhere else in the world! Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned! Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care.Image Products of California Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit https://www.imageproductsca.com (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you use our “Contact IPC (Info Request)” form in an attempt to communicate with us through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, company, phone number, email address, and country. We refer to this information as “Contact Form Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Contact Form Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Contact Form Information that we collect generally to communicate with you.We use the Device Information that we collect to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site.SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISINGImage Products of California does NOT engage in targeted advertisements or marketing communications. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.ONLINE ORDERINGThe Site does not accept orders and is for informational use only. When present, links to other sites will have their own privacy policies that are independent of Image Products of California’s privacy policy.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you use our “Contact IPC (Info Request)” form in order to communicate with us through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you contact us through the Site, we will maintain your Contact Form Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.MINORSThe Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please use our “Contact IPC (Info Request)” form link at the top of every page or by mail using the details provided below:PO Box 92241, Rochester, NY, 14692, United StatesQuick LinksCleaning BladesContact IPC (Info Request)DeveloperFuser RollersFuser WebsNew ProductsPhotoreceptorsPressure RollersProduct CatalogTonersLatest NewsImportant Information Regarding IPC
TechPartsAdditional Info Click here to request additional informationCompany Info Rochester, New York  USA Hours: Mon - Fri / 9:00AM - 5:00PM ESTPrivacy Policy StatementCookie DeclarationSite Map
The company names, product names, and part numbers listed are for descriptive purposes only to show compatibility.
© 2016 Image Products of California - All Rights Reserved.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.
If you continue to use this site, you accept our use of cookies.OkPrivacy Policy Statement
